playboystore.com 2018-10-23

# Privacy Policy – Playboy Shop

**PRIVACY POLICY**   
Effective April 15, 2015

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes Playboy’s data collection and use practices associated with the Playboy’s family of websites (the “Sites”). This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Policy here and changing the “Effective Date” at the top. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. By using or navigating our Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use or visit any of the Sites or any portion of the Sites.

Personal information collected on and/or through the Sites is stored and processed in the United States and by using any aspect of the Sites, you consent to the transfer of information outside of your country to the United States and to other countries.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**   
We may collect personal information that you provide to us such as your name, e-mail address, street address and telephone number. We may also collect your credit card number, credit card expiration date and banking information if such information is provided by you. We generally collect this personal information on our registration forms and our order forms when you sign up to receive products or services from any of the Sites. We may also collect information from our online surveys if you choose to participate, such as age, gender and income level. When you visit any of our Sites, we collect certain anonymous demographic information about you, including your IP address, zip code and browser program. We also collect information regarding your use of the Sites through the use of cookies (see below for more about cookies).

If you choose to post messages, comments, or other information in one of the public forums or other areas on any of our Sites, or on third party websites linked to any of the Sites (such our Facebook page, YouTube channel, or Tumblr) we will maintain such information about you as you choose to disclose in your posting.

Please review the privacy policy of each of your social networks to learn more about how you can control the dissemination of your personal information using such social networks’ privacy settings.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We will also maintain a record or notes of communications with you regarding your account.

**INFORMATION USAGE**   
We use your information in order to process your credit card payments, to fulfill your orders and/or requests, to facilitate your viewing and use of our Sites, to communicate with you, and to provide you with information about Playboy, as well as some of our partners and third party companies in which we think you may be interested. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and Site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally.

We use IP addresses, personal information, and anonymous demographic information to tailor your experiences at our Sites by showing content in which we think you will be interested and displaying content according to your preferences. Anonymous demographic information is shared with advertisers and market researchers on an aggregate basis.

We use information collected to evaluate and improve our services. We may develop and use, in our sole discretion, consumer research, which may be based on your use of our services.

**INFORMATION SHARING**   
In some cases, we will share information we collect (including personal information and/or anonymous demographic information) with third party companies who may offer products or services in which we believe you may be interested. We may also share personal information such as your name and/or email address with advertisers and market researchers to the extent permissible in accordance with applicable law. We also share this information with third parties with whom we partner to co-promote and administer sweepstakes and contests on our Site.

We may also share information we collect with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the Site and/or the services we provide, such as maintaining our servers and processing or fulfilling orders for products and services you purchase through the Site.

We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so by law, court order or governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of Playboy.

In the event of a change in ownership or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to another entity, including through bankruptcy, we reserve the right to transfer all user information collected in connection with the Site, including but not limited to email addresses, to a separate entity.

**OUR USE OF COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**   
Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored on your computer for future access. The Sites use cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making the Sites easier to navigate or to make a feature work better. Generally, cookies can be disabled at your discretion. However, you must accept cookies in order for certain parts of the Sites to work, including registration and posting comments. In addition, while you may always opt-out of receiving cookies, please note that your opt-out choices are device-specific and browser-specific, so if your preference is to opt out, you will need to do it for each of your devices and browsers. You may also delete your cookies, but that does not mean that all tracking will stop.

We may also use technology known as “web beacons” or single-pixel GIFs that allow us to count visitors to our Site and deliver co-branded services. Web beacons collect limited, non-personal information including cookie number, time and date of a page view and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides.

We do not honor Do Not Track requests at this time.

**INFORMATION SECURITY**   
Playboy takes reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you and to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. The personally identifiable information held by Playboy is stored in a secure location with limited administrative access.

**THIRD PARTY SITES**   
The Site may contain links to other websites. By clicking on any banner advertisement or other link, you will be redirected off the Site and to the applicable third party website. Playboy is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of such websites. You should make sure that you read and understand the privacy policies of these sites and direct any concerns regarding external links to the site administrator or webmaster of that third party website.

**CHOICE**   
All e-mails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe, and you may unsubscribe at any time. Additionally, you have the option to remove your information from our database by emailing [privacy@playboy.com](mailto:privacy@playboyshop.com).

You may correct or update the personal information you have provided to Playboy by sending us an email at [privacy@playboy.com](mailto:privacy@playboyshop.com).

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**   
California residents who have an established business relationship with Playboy may choose to opt out of the disclosure of their personal information about them to third parties for marketing purposes. From time to time, we may share your personal information with carefully screened companies that offer products or services that we believe you may enjoy. If you do not want us to share your personal information with such third parties, please send us a request opting out of such disclosures along with your name, e-mail address, street address and phone number to [privacy@playboy.com](mailto:privacy@playboyshop.com). Your opt-out request will be processed within 30 days of the date it is received.
